number six is the 2300
day prophecy and it brings us right back
to daniel 8 13
palomoni the wonderful number it is the
last
prophecy it is a prophecy that is
built upon in the book of revelation how
long shall be the vision concerning the
daily sacrifice and the transgression of
desolation to give both the sanctuary
and the host to be trodden under foot
unto 2 300 days then shall the sanctuary
be cleansed we know
that because it's in the book of daniel
it follows the same principle a day for
year
meaning that 2300 days are 2300
years in daniel chapter 8 verse 26
the same chapter in which this 2300 year
prophecy is given
daniel tells us that he did not
understand the vision
watch what he says wherefore shut thou
up the vision for it shall be for many
days
and i daniel fainted and was sick
certain days
afterward i rose up and did the king's
business and i was astonished at the
vision
but none understood it what does he
understand he doesn't understand the
2300 days
it is in daniel 9 that the angel comes
back
and gives daniel the starting point and
guess what the starting point is
know therefore and understand that from
the going forth of the commandment
to restore and to build jerusalem unto
the messiah the prince
so the beginning point of the 2300 years
is the same beginning point of the
70 weeks that we saw earlier if you take
when the decree went forth to rebuild
jerusalem and add 490 years we already
saw
that brings you to 34 a.d 490 of the
2300 years
brings us to 34 a.d meaning there are
years left if you add 1810
to 34ad you come to the year
1844. let me show you another graph just
so you can get the picture before i say
what i'm about to say and then close
457 bc this is when the prophecy begins
in daniel there is only one prophecy in
daniel
it's the 2300 years but the 70 weeks
and the 1260 are subsections
of that one prophecy so 457 to 34 a.d
is the first 490 years the 1260 years
occurs after that it is the midsection
of the prophecy
and then the final section of the
prophecy the 2300 days
that concludes in 1844 457
add 2300 years brings you
to 1844 the
challenge is this if you want to know
what the
final movement of god is all you got to
do is ask yourself
is there a movement that came on the
scene in 1844
and was there a fulfillment prophet
that came on the scene at the same time
as part of said movement now the odds of
that
would be absolutely crazy right it'd
just be astronomical
if there's no movement that arose in
1844 and no prophet that came on the
scene in 1844
hey it is what it is however
if god's divine math is accurate all i'm
inviting you to do
is search out the year 1844
and just see is there a movement that
came on the scene at that time
is there a prophet with that movement
that came on the scene
at that time that claims to follow the
bible that follows the prophets before
it
that speak of daniel and revelation
that's all i'm asking because if you
don't find that
then yeah this whole thing is just crazy
right because
it would just be way more than
coincidence
way more than coincidence for you to
take 2 300 years
and come from 457 bc and have the rise
of a movement of people that were not
even aware
of that prophecy meaning what it meant